

CONTACT ME AT

- Vera Cruz, Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil
- julio.frantz.dev@gmail.com

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Smart Contracts, Solidity, Rust
- Blockchain, Ethereum, Binance..
- NFT, ERC20, ERC721, DAPP, DEFI
- React.js, Redux, Gatsby.js, Next.js
- Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Laravel, Express
- JavaScript, TypeScript, Three.js
- AWS, Firebase
- UX/UI development (web and mobile)

EDUCATION



- Bachelor of Science degree in Electrical Engineering
- 2014 2016
- University of Minnesota -Minneapolis, MN, USA

JULIO FRANTZ

FRONT-END | BACK-END | BLOCKCHAIN

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a full-stack developer with blockchain tech experience. My main stack is developing reach & performant UX frontend using React.js and React Native.

This includes implementing the pixel-perfect and responsive web & mobile UI based on the design.

Nowadays, I am focusing on the Blockchain-based platform. I have hands-on experience with smart contracts, crypto wallet implementation, NFT Tokens, solidity, web3, as well as yield farming.

EMPLOYMENT

Senior Software Developer

web development | 2016 - 2016

Technologies: CSS3, TypeScript, Redux, React, JavaScript, Web Development, REST APIs, CSS

- Developed an application from the ground up; also configured the project structure and application skeleton.
- Created reusable React components for the date picker, dropdown, buttons, and input styles according to the provided designs.
- Delivered application screens: the login, reset password flow, and administration pages.

Ethereum/Solidity Developer

Kryptonex LLC | 2016 - 2016 Web3.js, Ethereum, Solidity

 Helped to integrate Ethereum and ER20 tokens into an exchange that is currently being built. It included address generation, token listing, and basic wallet operation related to ether and tokens using Web3.js.



CONTACT ME AT

- Vera Cruz, Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil
- julio.frantz.dev@gmail.com

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Smart Contracts, Solidity, Rust
- Blockchain, Ethereum, Binance..
- NFT, ERC20, ERC721, DAPP, DEFI
- React.js, Redux, Gatsby.js, Next.js
- Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Laravel, Express
- JavaScript, TypeScript, Three.js
- AWS, Firebase
- UX/UI development (web and mobile)

EDUCATION

- Bachelor of Science degree in Electrical Engineering
 - 2014 2016
 - University of Minnesota -Minneapolis, MN, USA

Senior Developer/Docker Evangelist

Max2, Inc. | 2016 - 2016

Technologies: Docker, Git, Cucumber, Spring, Java

- Introduced Docker to the development environment.
- Helped improve the CI pipeline.
- Extended the credit card portal.
- Improved the user journey experience for a loan portal.

Blockchain Engineer

Fan Hero | 2017 - 2017

Technologies: IPFS, Solidity, Ethereum

- Provided consultancy on Ethereum.
- Researched the use of permissioned blocks and IPFS.
- Investigated transferring tokens without ether.
- Prototyped a token contract.

Solidity Expert

Coinuma SL | 2018 - 2018

Technologies: Python, Web 3.0, Solidity, Ethereum

- Helped to integrate Ethereum into the cryptocurrency exchange being built.
- Demonstrated wallet generation, ether and token transfers, balance checks, and listening for events.
- Advised on best security practices.

Blockchain Engineer

IDEX - Aurora Labs S. A. | 2018 - 2018

Technologies: Node.js, Solidity, Ethereum

- Investigated various optimizations to Ethereum transaction throughput and gas cost for IDEX, currently the biggest on-chain exchange.
- Prototyped several optimizations including scheduling and specialized smart contracts.

Blockchain Engineer

LLPS, LLC. | 2019 - 2019

Technologies: Drizzle, React, DApps, Web 3.0, Solidity, Ethereum

- Built a prototype of a real estate-backed loans platform.
- Designed and built the Ethereum smart contracts forming the back end of the platform.
- Created a user interface to the blockchain back end using React and Drizzle.



CONTACT ME AT

- Vera Cruz, Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil
- julio.frantz.dev@gmail.com

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Smart Contracts, Solidity, Rust
- Blockchain, Ethereum, Binance..
- NFT, ERC20, ERC721, DAPP, DEFI
- React.js, Redux, Gatsby.js, Next.js
- Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Laravel, Express
- JavaScript, TypeScript, Three.js
- AWS, Firebase
- UX/UI development (web and mobile)

EDUCATION



- Bachelor of Science degree in Electrical Engineering
- 2014 2016
- University of Minnesota -Minneapolis, MN, USA

Ethereum Engineer

Zipmex Exchange. | 2019 - 2020

Technologies: Truffle, Solidity, Ethereum

- Created an upgradable erc20 token contract using a call delegate proxy.
- Deployed the project to mainnet, verified on Etherscan, and provided instructions to the team on how to use it.

Blockchain Engineer

British Asset – Kauri Crypto | 2020 - 2021 Technologies: JavaScript, GRAPH, Truffle, Solidity, Ethereum

- Created and deployed a staking contract for the platform token.
- Created a demo DApp for the staking contract.
- Implemented and deployed the graph for the staking contract tracking all events and allowing more advanced queries.